(Leonard:)If that was a movie, I would go see it.
(Penny:)I know, right?
(Penny:)Okay, let's see, what else?
I guess that's about it.
(Penny:)That's the story of Penny.
(Leonard:)Well, it sounds wonderful.
(Penny:)It was.
(Penny:)Until I fell in love with a jerk.
What is happening?
[MOUTHS]
I don't know.
(Penny:)Oh, God, you know,
four years I lived with him.
(Penny:)Four years.
That's like as long as high school.
(Sheldon:)It took you four years
to get through high school?
(Penny:)I just... I can't believe I trusted him.
(Leonard:)Should I say something?
I feel I should say something.
(Sheldon:)You? No, you'll only make it worse.
You wanna know the most pathetic part?
(Penny:)Even though I hate his lying,
cheating guts...
(Penny:)...I still love him.